(Leonard:)Will the gentleman from the great
state of denial yield for a question?
- I will yield.
- After we go through the exercise...
(Leonard:)...of an annoying series of votes,
which the gentleman will lose...
...does he intend to quit
if he does not get his way?
(Leonard:)- He does.
- We are the Army Ants. All those in favor?
(Penny:)Good afternoon and welcome
to today's Physics Bowl practice round.
(Penny:)I'm Penny,
and I'll be your host because...
(Penny:)...I didn't have anything else
to do on a Saturday afternoon...
(Penny:)...and isn't that just a little sad?
(Penny:)- Gentlemen, are you ready?
LEONARD: Yes.
HOWARD: Fire away.
- It's none of my business...
...but is a guy who can't speak
in front of women gonna hold you back?
Oh, he'll be okay once the women
are mixed into the crowd.
(Leonard:)He only has a problem
when they're one-on-one and smell nice.
(Penny:)Oh, thanks, Raj. It's vanilla oil.
(Leonard:)I was actually the one who noticed.
Okay, let's just start.
(Penny:)Okay, the first question
is on the topic of optics.
"What is the shortest light pulse
ever produced?"
[BUZZER SOUNDS]
(Penny:)- Dr. Cooper.
- Of course, the answer is 130 attoseconds.